Guide to the Atlantic Philanthropies Archives, 1982-2017.
Atlantic Philanthropies Archives,
- Series IV: Grant Files
  - Subseries H: South Africa grant files, 1980-2014
    - Nelson Mandela Metropolitan University (NMMU), 2007-2011; Nelson Mandela Metropolitan University
      - #15965. Strengthening institutional capacity-Lilitha Nursing College, 2007-2011 (Box 46, Folder 17-18)
    - Niall Mellon Township Trust, 2008-2009
      Niall Mellon Township Trust
      - #16751. Pilot factory for manufacture of timber-frame housing and associated advocacy and policy work, 2008-2009 (Box 46, Folder 19)
      - #16751. Pilot factory for manufacture of timber-frame housing and associated advocacy and policy work, 2008-2009 (Box 46, Folder 20)
    - Nkuzi Development Association, 2000-2006
      Shirinda, Shirhami
      Nkuzi Development Association
      - #8524 and #11742. Scholarship to Shirmhami Shirinda, 2000-2001, 2003 (Box 169, Folder 38)
        Dublin cabinet file Cab.1, Dr. 4B, 37/3/5
      - #8524. Scholarship for Shirhami Shirinda, 2000-2002 (Box 46, Folder 21)
      - #11742. Scholarship for Shirhami Shirinda, 2003-2005; Rural Legal Trust (Box 46, Folder 23)
    - North West University, 2006-2012; North-West University (South Africa)
      North-West University (South Africa)
      - The costed blue-print for the construction of the Resource and Learning Centre, Department of Nursing Science, North West University, Republic of South Africa, Undated (Box 22, Folder 5)
      - Proposed New Learning Resource Center for Nursing at the Mafikeng Campus of the North West University, Undated (Box 22, Folder 6)
      - #17440. Collaboration between Mafeking campus of North West University and McMaster University, Canada, 2006, 2008, 2010-2012 (Box 47, Folder 1-2)
        McMaster University
      - #17578. Center for Nursing Policy and Leadership Outcomes (CENPOLL), 2009-2010 (Box 47, Folder 3)
      - #17578. UNEDSA. Center for Nursing Policy and Leadership Outcomes (CENPOLL), 2008-08-15 (Box 47, Folder 4)
    - Nursing Education Association (NEA), 2007-2010; Nursing Education Association
      Nursing Education Association
      - #16548. Professionalizing the Nursing Education Association, 2007, 2009-2010 (Box 47, Folder 5)
      - #16907. Planning grant. To support NEA towards the growth and development into a professional organization, 2008-2009 (Box 47, Folder 6)
    - Office of Performing Arts and Film, 2010
      Office of Performing Arts and Film
      - #19145. Rewind: a TRC (Truth and Reconciliation Commission) Cantata. Dem-Con, 2010 (Box 47, Folder 7)
    - Other Foundation Trust, 2012-03-14
      Other Foundation Trust
      - #20010. The OTHER (Openess, Tolerance, Humanity, Equality, Rights) Foundation, 2012-03-14 (Box 47, Folder 8)
    - OUT (Tshwane), 2002-2007; OUT (Tshwame)
      OUT (Tshwane)
      - #12612. Core support. LGBTI, 2004-2006 (Box 47, Folder 9)
      - #12612. Core support. LGBTI (2), 2004-2007 (Box 47, Folder 10-12)
        - Levels of Empowerment of Gay and Lesbian People in Gauteng, CD-5265 (Box 47, Folder 10)
    - Out in Africa Committee, 2003-2008; Out in Africa (Film festival)
      - #12459. 10th Annual Gay and Lesbian Film Festival, 2003-2004 (Box 47, Folder 13-14)
      - #12459. 10th Annual Gay and Lesbian Film Festival, 2003-2004 (Box 169, Folder 39)
        Dublin cabinet file Cab. 1, Dr. 4B, 37/3/8
      - #13200. Core support. LGBTI (1), 2004-2008 (Box 47, Folder 15-18)
        - Out in Africa. Ermelo 2005. Recce and festival-pictures, 2005; CD-5266 (Box 47, Folder 15)
        - Telling Tales, DVD-3350 (Box 47, Folder 15)
        - The Heart of Hope: South Africa's Transition from Apartheid to Democracy, 2004; CD-5391; OâMalley, Padraig (Box 47, Folder 18)
      - #13200. Core support. LGBTI (2), 2003-2004 (Box 48, Folder 1-2)
    - Pietermaritzburg Gay and Lesbian Network, 2003-2008
      Pietermaritzburg Gay and Lesbian Network
      - #14416. Outreach support and services - start up, 2005-2006 (Box 48, Folder 3)
      - #14416. Outreach support and services- start up. LGBTI, 2003-2008 (Box 48, Folder 4-5)
    - Dr. Vicki Pinkney-Atkinson, 2009-2010; Pinkney-Atkinson, Vicki
      - #18722. Coordination of the UNEDSA program, 2009-2010 (Box 48, Folder 6)
        Pinkney-Atkinson, Vicki
    - Population Council, 2004-2009
      Population Council
      Special Population Support
      - #13511. Community participation in the rollout of HIV/AIDS treatment, 2004-2005 (Box 48, Folder 7)
      - #13511. CBOs participation in ARVs roll out, 2004-2009 (Box 48, Folder 8-9)
      - #13511. Comm. participation in HIV/AIDS treatment, 2004 (Box 48, Folder 10)
    - Program for Appropriate Technologies in Health-PATH, 2003-2012; Program for Appropriate Technology in Health
      Program for Appropriate Technology in Health
      - #12421. Advancing low-cost health technologies in South Africa, 2003-2005 (Box 48, Folder 11)
      - #12421. Advancing low-cost health technologies in SA, 2003-2005 (Box 48, Folder 12-13)
      - #14846. Strengthening the capacity of the public health system (health technologies for maternal and newborn care) 1, 2003-2005, 2008-2009 (Box 48, Folder 14-16)
      - #14846. Strengthening the capacity of the public health system. 2, 2006, 2008-2009, 2012 (Box 48, Folder 17-20)
    - Public Policy Partnership, 2002-2006
      Public Policy Partnership
      - #11595. Public Policy Partnership, 2003-2006 (Box 49, Folder 1)
      - #11595. Public Policy Partnership. National office, 2002-2006 (Box 49, Folder 2)
    - Red Cross Children's Hospital, 2002-2009; Red Cross War Memorial Children's Hospital
      Red Cross War Memorial Children's Hospital
      Children's Hospitals
      Surgery
      - #15570. Rebuilding and re-equipping operating theaters, 2007-2009 (Box 49, Folder 3)
      - #15570. Rebuilding and re-equipping the operating theaters, 2002-2003, 2006-2008 (Box 49, Folder 4)
    - Rhodes University Foundation, 2000-2012
      Rhodes University
      - #9995. Legal aid clinic, 2000-2007 (Box 49, Folder 5-6)
      - #9995. Legal Aid Clinic. R-Poor (rural poor), 2002-2004 (Box 49, Folder 7-8)
      - #9995. Legal clinic, 2001-2002 (Box 170, Folder 1)
        Dublin cabinet file Cab. 1, Dr. 4A, 37/2/9/1
      - #9995. RULAC (Legal Aid Clinic), 2011 (Box 49, Folder 9)
      - #10135. Sol Plaatje Media Leadership Institute, 2002, 2006 (Box 170, Folder 2)
        Dublin cabinet file 37/2/9
        Journalism
      - #10135. Sol Plaatje Media Leadership Institute, 2001-2010 (Box 49, Folder 10-11)
      - #10842. Centenary Campaign, 2002, 2004 (Box 170, Folder 3)
        Dublin cabinet file 37/2/9/2
      - #10842. Centenary Campaign, 2001-2011 (Box 49, Folder 12-13)
      - #11217. MBA environ. management, 2002-2009 (Box 49, Folder 14-15)
      - #11217. Masters in Business Administration (environmental management), 2003 (Box 170, Folder 4)
        Dublin cabinet file 37/2/9/3
      - #11852. Department of Journalism and Media Studies: David Rabkin Unit for Experiential Journalism, 2003-2004 (Box 170, Folder 5)
        Dublin cabinet file 37/2/9/5
      - #11852. D. Rabkin writing school (Department of Journalism and Media Studies: David Rabkin Unit for Experiential Journalism), 2003-2008 (Box 49, Folder 16-17)
      - #11933. Equity Devel. Program, 2003-2010 (Box 50, Folder 1-2)
      - #13497. Rhodes University Legal Aid Clinic, 2004-2005, 2008 (Box 50, Folder 3)
      - #13497. Rhodes Legal Aid Clinic. R-Poor. (rural poor), 2002, 2004-2008 (Box 50, Folder 4-7)
      - #16180. Legal Aid Clinic, 2007-2008 (Box 50, Folder 8)
      - #16180. Legal Aid Clinic, 2001, 2007-2010 (Box 50, Folder 9-10)
      - #21273. Legacies of Apartheid, 2011-2012 (Box 50, Folder 11)
    - Robben Island Museum, 1999-2004
      Robben Island Museum
      - #8729. Gateway facility, Cape Town Waterfront, 1999-2002 (Box 170, Folder 6)
        Dublin cabinet file Cab. 1, Dr. 4D, 37/4/5/3
      - #8729. Gateway facility, Cape Town Waterfront, 1999-2002 (Box 50, Folder 12)
      - #10564. Padraig O'Malley South African study and archive, 2002, 2004 (Box 50, Folder 13)
        O'Malley, Padraig
      - #10564. Padraig O'Malley South African study and archive, 2002, 2004 (Box 50, Folder 14)
      - #10564. Padraig O'Malley South African study and archive. Dem-Con. (democracy-constitution), 2000-03 (Box 50, Folder 15)
    - Rural Legal Trust, 1997-2009
      - #8913. Rural Legal Trust, 2004 (Box 50, Folder 16)
        Agricultural Development
      - #8913. Rural Legal Trust. R-Poor (rural poor), 1997, 2000-2004 (Box 50, Folder 17-18)
      - #8913. Rural Legal Trust, 2001-2004, 2005 (Box 50, Folder 19)
      - #8913. Rural Legal Trust, 2001, 2007 (Box 50, Folder 20)
      - #8913. Rural Legal Trust; #12692. Farm dweller eviction survey, 2001, 2003-2005 (Box 46, Folder 22)
        Farm Bureaus and Granges
      - #12692. Farm dweller eviction survey, 2003-2006; Rural Legal Trust (Box 46, Folder 24-25)
      - #12692. Farm-dweller eviction survey, 2004 (Box 50, Folder 21)
      - #13591. Legal Aid Board pilot project, 2005-2007 (Box 50, Folder 22-23)
      - #13591. Legal Aid Board pilot project, 2005 (Box 50, Folder 24)
      - #15553. Legal support to farm workers, 2006-2009 (Box 50, Folder 25)
        - Review of the Pilot Project, 2005-2008, 2008; CD-5267 (Box 50, Folder 25)
    - Sabre Foundation, 1996-2001
      Sabre Foundation
      - #7645 (#98-14). Book donation program, 1996-2001 (Box 51, Folder 1)
    - SANGONeT, 2003-2006
      SANGONeT
      Websites
      - #11728. Thusanang fundraising portal, 2003-2006 (Box 51, Folder 2)
      - #11728. Thusanang fundraising portal, 2003, 2006 (Box 51, Folder 3)
    - Shikaya Facing the Past Project, 2008-2013; Shikaya (Organization)
      Shikaya (Organization)
      - #17953. Where do I stand? (a documentary film). Ref-Mig. (refugee-migrants), 2008-2010, 2012-2013 (Box 51, Folder 4)
      - #17953. Where do I stand? - a documentary film, 2009 (Box 51, Folder 5)
      - #19434. Growing leaders intervention, 2010 (Box 51, Folder 6)
      - #19434. Growing leaders project. Ref-Mig. (refugee-migrants), 2010 (Box 51, Folder 7)
    - Social Surveys - Africa, 2007-2010; Social Surveys (Pty)
      Social Surveys (Pty)
      - #17379. Barriers to access to education study, 2007-2010 (Box 51, Folder 8)
      - #17379. Barriers to access to education study, 2009 (Box 51, Folder 9)
      - #17589. Homophobia base-line data study, 2007-2010 (Box 51, Folder 10-12)
      - #17589. Homophobia base-line data study, 2009 (Box 51, Folder 13)
    - South Africa Partners, Inc, 2009-2010; South Africa Partners, Inc.
      South Africa Partners, Inc.
      - #17996. Capacity plan for building of health management project, 2009 (Box 51, Folder 14)
      - #19443. Planning and capacity building, 2010 (Box 51, Folder 15)
    - South African Graduates Development Association, 2001-2002
      South African Graduates Development Association
      - #9689. Graduates summit, 2001-2002 (Box 51, Folder 16)
      - #9689. Graduates summit, 2001 (Box 51, Folder 17)
    - South African History Archive (SAHA), 2001-2009; South African History Archive
      South African History Archive
      - #9674. Promotion of Access to Information Act, 2001-2004 (Box 51, Folder 18)
      - #9674. Promotion of Access to Information Act, 2002-2004 (Box 51, Folder 19)
      - #9674. Promotion of Access to Information Act, 2001, 2003 (Box 51, Folder 20)
      - #10999. Acquisition of three collections, 2002-2006 (Box 51, Folder 21-23)
      - #10999. Acquisition of three collections, 2002-2005 (Box 170, Folder 7)
        Dublin cabinet file 37/2/14/1
      - #12709. Core support: Apartheid records collection, 2004-2005, 2007 (Box 51, Folder 24)
      - #12709. Core support: Apartheid records collection. Struggles for Justice, 2004-2008 (Box 51, Folder 25-27)
      - #14804.Â Â Sunday Times heritage project, 2004, 2006-2009 (Box 52, Folder 1-3)
      - #14804. Â Sunday Times heritage project: lesson plans, Undated (Box 22, Folder 7)
      - #14804. Â Sunday Times heritage project, 2006-2007 (Box 52, Folder 4)
      - #15881. Publication of struggle posters book, 2007 (Box 52, Folder 5)
      - #15881. Publication of resistance posters, 2006-2007 (Box 52, Folder 6)
    - South African Institute for Advancement, 2002-2013; Inyathelo - South African Institute for Advancement
      - #15873. Inyathelo Institute of Advancement: strengthening the sustainability of rural NPOs, 2007 (Box 52, Folder 7)
      - #15873. Strengthening sustainability for rural NPOs, 2007, 2010 (Box 52, Folder 8)
      - #15998. Nursing education program, 2002, 2006-2009 (Box 52, Folder 9)
      - #15998. Nursing education program, 2007-2009 (Box 52, Folder 10)
      - #16017. Strengthening of institutional capacity, 2007-2008 (Box 52, Folder 11)
      - #16017. Strengthening of institutional capacity. SSC, 2007-2008 (Box 52, Folder 12)
      - #16181. Sustainability of rural poor. R-poor., 2007-2011, 2013 (Box 52, Folder 13)
      - #17952. Research project NDA and national lotteries. Dem-con. (democracy-constitution), 2009-2010 (Box 52, Folder 14)
      - #17952. Research project: funding practices of the National Development Agency and the National Lotteries. Reconciliation and Human Rights, 2009, 2011 (Box 52, Folder 15)
      - #19441. Donors conference, 2010 (Box 52, Folder 16)
    - South African Nursing Council, 2011-2013
      South African Nursing Council
      - #15699. Institutional support to the South African Nursing Council (SANC), 2011-2013 (Box 52, Folder 17)
    - Southern Africa Legal Services Foundation, 1980-2009
      Southern Africa Legal Services Foundation
      Audio Recording
      - #16759. Oral history project, 1980, 2006-2008 (Box 52, Folder 18)
      - #18828. Oral history project, 1980, 2006, 2009 (Box 52, Folder 19)
    - Southern African Grantmakers Association (SAGA), 1996-2005; Southern African Grantmakers Association
      Southern African Grantmakers Association
      - Reinventing SAGA contract, 2001 (Box 52, Folder 20)
      - #7473 (#97-1). Directory of grantmakers, 1996-1997, 2000 (Box 52, Folder 21)
        Some material in Afrikaans
      - #7473 (#97-1). Directory of grantmakers, 1996-1998 (Box 52, Folder 22)
      - #10748. Institutional support, 2001-2003, 2005 (Box 52, Folder 23)
      - #10748. Institutional support, 2002, 2005 (Box 52, Folder 24)
      - #10748. Institutional support. Dem-con (democracy-constitution), 2004 (Box 52, Folder 25-26)
      - #10748. Institutional support. Reports. R-poor (rural poor), 2002-2004 (Box 52, Folder 27-28)
    - Southern African HIV Clinicians Society, 2002-2010
      Southern African HIV Clinicians Society
      Immunology
      - #14816. Institutional support to Southern African HIV Clinicians Society, 2006-2009 (Box 53, Folder 1)
      - #14816. Strengthening the institutional capacity. Folder 1, 2002-2008, 2010 (Box 53, Folder 2-5)
      - #14816. Strengthening the institutional capacity. Folder 2, 2006-2008 (Box 53, Folder 6-8)
        - HIV Clinicians Society proposal, CD-5268 (Box 53, Folder 6)
    - Strategy and Tactics, 2009-2010; S and T (Firm)
      - #17382. Civil society response to xenophobia study (Strategy and Tactics). REF-MIG (refugees-migrants), 2009-2010 (Box 53, Folder 9)
      - #17382. Civil society response to xenophobia study (Strategy and Tactics), 2009 (Box 53, Folder 10)
    - Studies in Policy and Inequality Institute (SPII), 2006-2013; Studies in Policy and Inequality Institute
      Studies in Policy and Inequality Institute
      - #15171. Set-up costs, 2007-2008 (Box 53, Folder 11)
      - #15171. Core support. R-Poor (rural poor), 2006-2010 (Box 53, Folder 12-13)
      - #18772. Core support, 2009-2013 (Box 53, Folder 14-15)
    - Synergos Institute, 2003-2005
      Synergos Institute
      - #11216. Global Philanthropy and Foundation Building Program, 2003-2005 (Box 53, Folder 16)
    - Synergos Institute, Southern Africa, 2004-2010
      Synergos Institute, Southern Africa
      Atlantic Philanthropies (Organization)
      - #13198. Atlantic/HIVOS/Synergos Institution Building Initiative (LGBTs), 2004-2007 (Box 53, Folder 17)
      - #13198. Atlantic/HIVOS/Synergos Institution building initiative (LGBTs), 2004-2006 (Box 53, Folder 18)
      - #16018. AP/HIVOS capacity building. LGBTI, 2007-2010 (Box 53, Folder 19)
      - #16018. Atlantic/ HIVOS/ Synergos capacity building program for the gay and lesbian sector, 2007-2008, 2010 (Box 53, Folder 20)
    - Tertiary Education Network (TENET), 1997-2010; Tertiary Education and Research Network of South Africa
      Tertiary Education and Research Network of South Africa
      Internet
      - #8716. South African bandwidth initiative, 2000-2003 (Box 54, Folder 1)
      - #8716. Â South African bandwidth initiative, 2007-2008, 2010 (Box 54, Folder 2)
      - #8716 (#00-48). Bandwidth initiative, 1997-2001 (Box 54, Folder 3-5)
    - Topsy Foundation, 2004-2006
      Topsy Foundation
      - #13294. Comprehensive model - mitigating the impact of HIV/AIDS, 2004-2006 (Box 54, Folder 6)
      - #13294. Mitigating HIV/AIDS impact, 2004 (Box 54, Folder 7)
      - #13294. Mitigating the impact of HIV/AIDS: a comprehensive model, 2004-2005 (Box 54, Folder 8)
    - Treatment Action Campaign (TAC), 2001-2011; Treatment Action Campaign
      - #10034. Institutional support, 2001-2002, 2004 (Box 54, Folder 9)
      - #10034. Institutional support, 2002, 2005-2006 (Box 54, Folder 10)
      - #10034. Institutional support, 2001-2004 (Box 170, Folder 8)
        Dublin cabinet file Cab.1, Dr. 4B, 37/4/9
      - #12644. Treatment literacy program and operational support, 2004-2005 (Box 54, Folder 11)
      - #15039. Treatment literacy, 2006-2008 (Box 54, Folder 12-13)
      - #15039. Treatment literacy, 2006-2007, 2009, 2011 (Box 54, Folder 14)
      - #15191. Bridging funds, 2006-2007 (Box 54, Folder 15)
      - #18985. To develop TAC's model districts in Mopani and uMgungundlovu, 2003-2004 (Box 54, Folder 16)
    - Treatment Development Trust, 2005-2007
      Treatment Development Trust
      - #14205. Purchase of offices - TAC, 2005-2007 (Box 54, Folder 17)
    - Triangle Project, 2004-2005; Triangle Project (Cape Town, South Africa)
      Triangle Project (Cape Town, South Africa)
      - #12611. Core support, 2004-2007 (Box 54, Folder 18-19)
      - #12611. Core support, 2004-2006 (Box 54, Folder 20)
      - #12611. Core support. LGBTI, 2005 (Box 54, Folder 21-22)
    - Tshwane University of Technology Advancement Office, 2006-2011; Tshwane University of Technology. Advancement Office
      Tshwane University of Technology. Advancement Office
      - #17446. UNEDSA. Developing a community of practice education model, 2006-2008, 2010-2011 (Box 54, Folder 23-24)
      - #17446. Developing a community of practice education model, 2009 (Box 54, Folder 25)
    - Umanyano Publications, 2002-2005
      Umanyano Publications
      - #10868. South African Labour Bulletin, 2002-2005 (Box 54, Folder 26)
      - #10868. South African Labour Bulletin, 2002-2005 (Box 54, Folder 27)
    - Umthombo Youth Development Foundation, 2008-2011
      Umthombo Youth Development Foundation
      - #16552. Recruitment and training of students in rural KZN (KwaZulu-Natal). Population health, 2008-2009, 2011 (Box 55, Folder 1)
      - #16552. Recruitment and training of students in rural KZN (KwaZulu-Natal), 2008-2009 (Box 55, Folder 2)
    - University of Cape Town Development Office (UCT), 1995-2013; University of Cape Town. Development Office
      - General 2000-2001, 2000-2001 (Box 55, Folder 3)
      - General 2001-2006, 2001-2003, 2005-2006 (Box 55, Folder 4)
      - #7328 (#95-37). Law faculty LLM scholarships, 1995-1997 (Box 55, Folder 5)
      - #7328 (#95-37). UCT - School for Advanced Legal Studies, 1994-1999 (Box 170, Folder 9)
        Dublin cabinet file 37/3/1/2
      - #7475 (#97-3). Faculty diversification pilot program, 1996-1999 (Box 55, Folder 6)
      - #7475. Law School - Staff development program (faculty diversification pilot program), 1996-1999, 2001 (Box 170, Folder 10-11)
        Dublin cabinet file 37/3/1/2/2
      - #7518 (#97-45). Vice Chancellor's discretionary fund, 1996-2001, 2003 (Box 55, Folder 7)
      - #7518. UCT Vice Chancellor's discretionary fund, 1997-1999 (Box 170, Folder 12)
        Dublin cabinet file Cab. 4, Dr. 1A 37/2/2/1
      - #7609 (#97-136). Development Director recruitment, 1997-2001 (Box 55, Folder 8)
      - #7609 (#97-136). Development Director recruitment, 1997-1999, 2003 (Box 55, Folder 9)
      - #7609. UCT - fundraising (Development Director recruitment), 1997-2002 (Box 170, Folder 13-14)
        Dublin cabinet file Cab. 4, Dr. 1A 37/2/2/2
      - #7609. UCT - Development Director recruitment. Phase II, 1999-2000 (Box 170, Folder 15)
        Dublin cabinet file Cab. 4, Dr. 1A 37/2/2/2/1. Chiefly contains records on grant #7873
      - #7609. UCT - Development Director recruitment. Phase 3, 1999-2002 (Box 170, Folder 16)
        Dublin cabinet file Cab. 4, Dr. 1A 37/2/2/2/2. Chiefly contains records on grant #7984 (#00-7)
      - #7660 (#98-27). Law faculty profile of the legal profession, 1995-1996, 1998 (Box 55, Folder 10)
      - #7660 (#98-27). Profile of South African legal profession in terms of race and gender: first stage of research project, 1995-1999 (Box 55, Folder 11)
      - #7739. Departments of Biochemistry and Microbiology. Staff development. Folder 1, 1998-2009 (Box 55, Folder 12)
      - #7739. Departments of Biochemistry and Microbiology. Staff development. Folder 2, 1998-2006, 2008 (Box 55, Folder 13)
      - #7739 (#98-109). UCT - GOOT (Growing Our Own Timber) (Departments of Biochemistry and Microbiology), 1998-2005, 2007 (Box 170, Folder 17)
        Dublin cabinet file Cab.1, Dr. 4B, 37/2/2/3
      - #7847 (#99-56). Children's Institute. Planning grant., 1999-2000 (Box 55, Folder 14)
      - #7847. UCT - Children's Institute, 1997, 1999-2002 (Box 170, Folder 18)
        Dublin cabinet file Cab.1, Dr. 4A, 37/2/2/4
      - #7856 (#99-64). Public seminar, 1999 (Box 55, Folder 15)
      - #7856. UCT - conference on reconciliation, 1998-2001 (Box 170, Folder 19)
        Dublin cabinet file Cab.1, Dr. 4A, 37/2/2/5. Contains newspaper clippings in Afrikaans.
      - #7872 (#99-79). Law faculty staff development program, 1999-2002 (Box 55, Folder 16)
      - #7872. Law School - Staff development program, phase 2, 1999-2000 (Box 170, Folder 20)
        Dublin cabinet 37/3/1/2/2/1
      - #7873 (#99-80). Expansion development, 1999-2003 (Box 55, Folder 17)
        See also Box 170, folder 13
      - #7978 (#00-2). Transition fund, 1999, 2001, 2003 (Box 55, Folder 18)
      - #7978. UCT - Vice-Chancellor succession, 1999-2000 (Box 170, Folder 21)
        Dublin cabinet file Cab. 4, Dr. 1A 37/2/2/6
      - #7984 (#00-7). Development office software, 2000, 2002 (Box 55, Folder 19)
        See also Box 170, folder 14
      - #8278. Law faculty Oliver Tambo Moot court room, 2000-2001 (Box 55, Folder 20)
      - #8278. UCT - Graduate School of the Humanities (Oliver Tambo Moot court room), 1999-2000 (Box 170, Folder 22)
        Dublin cabinet file Cab. 4, Dr. 1A 37/2/2/7
      - #8694. Faculty in law: lecturer in human rights laws, 2001 (Box 55, Folder 21)
      - #8694. Faculty of law lecturer's post, 2000-2006 (Box 55, Folder 22)
      - #8726. Children's Institute, faculty of health sciences, 2000-2007 (Box 55, Folder 23-24)
      - #8726. UCT - Children's Institute - establishment, 2001, 2003, 2005, 2007 (Box 170, Folder 23)
        Dublin cabinet file Cab. 4, Dr. 1A 37/2/2/4/1
      - #8919. Globalization conference, 2000-2001 (Box 55, Folder 25)
      - #8919. UCT - globalization conference, 2001 (Box 170, Folder 24)
        Dublin cabinet file Cab. 4, Dr. 2B 37/2/2/11